- Hi!
- Hi.
(Guy:)I love your movie.
(Penny:)Well, thanks.
(Guy:)It has got to be
one of the worst things
(Guy:)I've ever seen in my life.
(Penny:)Your love confuses me.
(Leonard:)Would you like
an autograph?
(Guy:)Sure.
(Penny:)Okay. Who do I make it out to?
(Guy:)Daniel.
(Leonard:)- Okay.
- I have to ask.
(Daniel:)Were you trying to be that bad,
(Daniel:)or are you just
a terrible actress?
(Penny:)That did not clear things up.
That'll be $4.75.
(Daniel:)Keep the change.
But I... Oh.
(Leonard:)Nothing about that
was good.
Mm-mm.
(Amy:)There's nothing
to be afraid of, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)The average cork speed
is 25 miles per hour.
(Sheldon:)If that is too fast
around a school,
(Sheldon:)it is certainly too fast
around a kitchen.